{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"An array is;","correct_answer":"Lists of data","incorrect_answers":["Sizes","Options","Shapes"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What is first index value of an array?","correct_answer":"0","incorrect_answers":["-1","1","undefine"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What surrounds an array?","correct_answer":"Square Brackets","incorrect_answers":["Curly Brackets","Parenthesis","Quotations"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"array = [1,2,3,4,5] What is the length of this array?","correct_answer":"5","incorrect_answers":["4","0","125.4"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which definition below best describe an array?","correct_answer":"An array is a special variable, which can hold more than one value at a time.","incorrect_answers":["An array is a beam of light.","An array is a function identifier that can hold more than one parameter.","An array is a special function, which can hold more than one value at a time."]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What is proper syntax for declaring a array in JavaScript?","correct_answer":"var arrayName =[ ];","incorrect_answers":["var arrayName[ ] ={ };","array arrayName ={ };","obj var arrayName =[ ];"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which of the variables below is an array?","correct_answer":"var names = [];","incorrect_answers":["var names = array;","var names='array'","var names[];"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"The push() method adds a new element to the end of an array?","correct_answer":"true","incorrect_answers":["false"," "," "]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How would you change the first element in an array?","correct_answer":"nums[0] = 'New!';","incorrect_answers":["nums = 'New!';","var nums[1] = 'New!';","nums[1] = 'New!';"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"array = [1,2,3,4,5]; What is the highest position in this array? HINT: Remember arrays start at position 0!","correct_answer":"4","incorrect_answers":["5","0","125.7"]}]}

